amahi.org 2009-06-20

# Amahi Home Server

## In Short

Your privacy is very important to us.

Your privacy and personally-identifying information (email, and any personally-identifiable information that is not publicly available on the site) will not be shared without your explicit permission, or unless required to operate our services or comply by law.

We will only ask for information that is truly needed to give you a better service.

Please go on to the actual details of the policy.

[ ](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) We've decided to adopt the Privacy Policy adapted from our friends at [wordpress.com](http://wordpress.com/), which they graciously made available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license.

## Amahi Privacy Policy

Amahi Inc. (“ **Amahi** ”) operates several websites including [amahi.org](http://www.amahi.org/) and subdomains (blog, wiki, etc.). It is Amahi’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Amahi collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Amahi's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Amahi's visitors use its website. From time to time, Amahi may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Amahi also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Amahi does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Amahi’s websites choose to interact with Amahi in ways that require Amahi to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Amahi gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at [amahi.org](http://www.amahi.org/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Amahi – by purchasing services, for example – will be asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Amahi collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Amahi. Amahi does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website- and service-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Amahi may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Amahi may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Amahi does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Amahi discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Amahi’s behalf or to provide services available at Amahi’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Amahi’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Amahi will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Amahi discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Amahi believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Amahi, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Amahi website and have supplied your email address, Amahi may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Amahi and our products. We primarily use our blog and newsletter to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Amahi takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Amahi uses cookies to help Amahi identify and track visitors, their usage of Amahi website, and their website access preferences. Amahi visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Amahi’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Amahi’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Amahi may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Amahi’s sole discretion. Amahi encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a amahi.org account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
